<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<job-search>
  <jobs total="59557" count="5" start="0">
    <job>
      <id>13256276</id>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Big Four practice is composed of more than 2,300 resources with significant industry and technical expertise in a broad range of risk and compliance issues. &lt;br&gt;  &lt;br&gt;They help companies achieve the confidence needed for strong three lines of defense on risk by: &lt;br&gt;  &lt;br&gt;-Building and fortifying internal and IT risk controls &lt;br&gt;  -Developing and strengthening risk and compliance programs &lt;br&gt;  -Improving the capabilities of Internal Audit function &lt;br&gt;  &lt;br&gt;They draw proudly on thier auditing heritage as well as our commercial experience to rigorously evaluate and implement a companies governance procedures, processes, information, and controls. They provide broad support across a business to elevate trust and transparency, protect the business and give all parties assurance that risks are fully anticipated, understood, and managed strategically. &lt;br&gt;  &lt;br&gt;The Risk Assurance practice operates nationally to assist risk, compliance, &amp;amp; finance departments of Fortune 500 companies in using data to make better decisions and get faster results through the use of analytics, strategy, tools and data governance. Within the Financial Services space the team focuses on business topics such as AML, Trade Compliance, Regulatory Reporting and Fraud. Within Healthcare the team is focused on topics such as ICD-10, revenue cycle, meaningful use, PCMH, care coordination, healthcare reform and Fraud. Their services range from hands on analytics to strategy projects related to helping organizations transform themselves to use more analytics across their departments. A sample of their services includes: &lt;br&gt;  &lt;br&gt;- Model Development and Tuning &lt;br&gt;  - System Assessment &lt;br&gt;  - Dashboard Development &lt;br&gt;  - Analytics Strategy &lt;br&gt;  - Continuous Monitoring&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </job>
    <job>
      <id>13256189</id>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;SEAL Consulting Inc is looking to hire Senior / Architect level resources in SAP Hybris area in USA. These resources are expected to work at our client sites in complex system environments.  Candidate should have passion for learning, long term commitment and ability to take up responsibility.  Should be willing to take up new challenges and work on complex issues both independently and as part of a team and should be eager to assume responsibility quickly.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </job>
    <job>
      <id>13256176</id>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;SEAL Consulting Inc is looking to hire Senior and Architect level resources in SAP Ariba in USA. These resources are expected to work at our client sites in complex system environments.  Candidate should have passion for learning, long term commitment and ability to take up responsibility.  Should be willing to take up new challenges and work on complex issues both independently and as part of a team and should be eager to assume responsibility quickly.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </job>
    <job>
      <id>13256161</id>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Top Midtown Manhattan Law Firm has an immediate need for a senior Desktop Packaging &amp;amp; Deployment Engineer. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Firm,. located in Midtown Manhattan is looking for someone to work as a consultant for 4-6 Months with the option to convert the engineer to a permanent employee once the contract is up.   The position is one that offers a great deal of responsibility, as you will be a senior member of a 5 person team &amp;amp; also offers growth &amp;amp; mentoring opportunity for the right person. The work environment is excellent &amp;amp; the people are great to work with. If you are qualified &amp;amp; interested please APPLY NOW or email alex@jmd-partners.com  for immediate consideration.  The ideal candidate will have experience packaging applications from Windows XP to Windows 7 (32 Bit) in a mid sized (1000+ User) environment.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;Duties : &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. Design and maintain workstation images&lt;br&gt;  2. Maintain and troubleshoot Group Policy.&lt;br&gt;  3. Design automated installation processes for Microsoft&#39;s standard installer technology (MSI), and other virtual streaming technologies.&lt;br&gt;  4. Troubleshoot desktop-related issues in coordination with other members of IS and users, when necessary.&lt;br&gt;  5. Keep up-to-date on patches and security fixes available for our workstation Operating System.&lt;br&gt;  6. Recommend ways of improving our desktop architecture.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </job>
    <job>
      <id>13256150</id>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Top Midtown Manhattan Law Firm has an immediate need for a senior Desktop Packaging &amp;amp; Deployment Engineer. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Firm,. located in Midtown Manhattan is looking for someone to work as a consultant for 4-6 Months with the option to convert the engineer to a permanent employee once the contract is up.   The position is one that offers a great deal of responsibility, as you will be a senior member of a 5 person team &amp;amp; also offers growth &amp;amp; mentoring opportunity for the right person. The work environment is excellent &amp;amp; the people are great to work with. If you are qualified &amp;amp; interested please APPLY NOW or email alex@jmd-partners.com  for immediate consideration.  The ideal candidate will have experience packaging applications from Windows XP to Windows 7 (32 Bit) in a mid sized (1000+ User) environment.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;Duties : &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. Design and maintain workstation images&lt;br&gt; 2. Maintain and troubleshoot Group Policy.&lt;br&gt; 3. Design automated installation processes for Microsoft&#39;s standard installer technology (MSI), and other virtual streaming technologies.&lt;br&gt; 4. Troubleshoot desktop-related issues in coordination with other members of IS and users, when necessary.&lt;br&gt; 5. Keep up-to-date on patches and security fixes available for our workstation Operating System.&lt;br&gt; 6. Recommend ways of improving our desktop architecture.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </job>
  </jobs>
</job-search>
