<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<job-search>
  <jobs total="59553" count="5" start="0">
    <job>
      <id>13254960</id>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We are seeking a truly exceptional emerging leader to join our team as our Director of HR &amp;amp; Talent Management for a rapidly growing Digital Strategy and Innovation business. In this new role, you’ll work across the organization to implement scalable solutions, programs and processes designed to help develop our talent. Our talent is core to our business so the ideal candidate understands how this position will be instrumental in building and growing a large organization of high performing talent.  This role will report to the President &amp;amp; Chief Operating Officer and will have a measurable impact on top and bottom line growth. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Talent Acquisition&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Identify and leverage sources of talent that can be quickly recruited for spikes in demand (contractors and employees) for evergreen roles such as Engagement Managers, Project Managers, Product Managers, Digital Analysts, Digital Strategists, Experience Designers, Experience Developer, Platform / System Integration / Backend Developers, etc. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Minimize the costs of recruiting best in class talent by optimizing the use of internal referral programs, networking through LinkedIn, direct posting to LinkedIn and other job boards, and outside recruiters. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Refine and evangelize an employee candidate referral program to incent high performing team members to refer candidates to open positions and general roles and keep talent acquisition top of employees minds. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Streamline process for quickly creating job descriptions that eliminates customization of common sections (e.g. general requirements, company overview) and lead development of each job description, minimizing burden on hiring managers. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Manage applicant tracking system (currently RecruiterBox.com) and ensure it is up to date and used appropriately across organization.  Continually streamline process around tool and ensure usage policies of tool are documented on intranet. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Refine on-boarding process that efficiently and comfortably transitions new employees into the organization and provides the appropriate information that will help make them successful. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Talent Development&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Develop training programs across all facets of the business to develop employee skills and knowledge (Developing trainings yourself and incorporating external partners as needed). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Partner with division leads to define and develop Vimeo’s people strategy, helping to ensure that solutions, programs and practices implemented are scalable for the business. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Provide coaching and consulting to managers and employees in the areas of performance management, performance counseling, compensation, employee retention, talent planning, leader development, and employee development. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Define competencies and experience required for specific jobs and levels. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Performance Management&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Own the performance management process, make recommendations for programs/initiative designed to reward and recognize employees. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lead evaluation and recommendation best in class cloud based performance management solution to track goals, performance, performance reviews, etc.  Implement solution and process across employees and supervisors. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Refine the performance management process to promote consistent and timely  meritocracy and ensure it is documented and communicated and understood by all employees and candidates. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brief talent managers on common themes for administering performance management and how to leverage tools to ensure consistent best practices across company. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Refine approach to turnaround or manage remedial performance management situations. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gather, review and analyze data to identify trends and recommend solutions to improve performance, retention and engagement. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Compensation &amp;amp; Benefits&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Refine bonus methodology and calculations to tie to performance management process and annual goal setting. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Maintain compensation benchmarking analysis, ensuring that compensation is competitive and internally consistent. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rationalize band levels within organization and begin to standardize compensation &amp;amp; benefit ranges. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Refine process to communicate and administer raises, bonuses and other benefits in a timely manner. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Evaluate creative benefits that are low cost and high value to employees and the Company. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Collaborate with Finance Director to ensure payroll execution aligns with additions or changes in benefits. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Employee Communications, Culture &amp;amp; Relations&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Drive communications that keep employees abreast of company developments (new clients, new projects, successes, new team members) whether ensuring they are sent by appropriate person or sending yourself. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Develop and calendarize team activities (e.g. happy hours, office lunches, group activities, etc.)  for main office that also have appropriate comparable activities for satellite offices that foster team building and employee culture. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oversee company event strategy and execution (including quarterly company-wide events, small team events, annual off-site event, occasional theme days) with an eye towards connecting our employees. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Policy, Administration &amp;amp; Compliance&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Drive completion and regular updates of intranet and other company communication covers all necessary topics. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Identify and propose policy and administration changes to any program to ensure Centric Digital is in compliance &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Collaborate with general counsel and finance to recommend appropriate changes to policies, processes, systems, intranet, employment contracts and record keeping that will maintain with Federal, State and City laws. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Organizational Design &amp;amp; Training&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Will work with Senior Leadership team on changes to organizational structure that respond to business changes, ensure job satisfaction and make the best use of talent as Centric Digital continues to grow &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Identify skill gaps within the organization and propose training or organizational shifts to close the gaps &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </job>
    <job>
      <id>13254920</id>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration:underline&quot;&gt;Overview&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Be part of a team that’s not just talking about revolutionizing the payments industry, but is actually in position to make it happen.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;/em&gt;Our group is transforming the payments landscape through our loyalty and virtual gift card products, helping merchants better understand their customers and giving them the tools to drive increased visits and sales.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Perka is an innovative mobile loyalty solution that targets both SMB merchants as well as the largest retailers in the world.  Helping to educate and sell into these diverse customer segments will be a key part of the Product Specialist’s role.   Perka has 3 main product variations and the Product Specialist would need to become a subject matter expert on all 3 solutions, helping merchants understand which is right for them, and how they compare to other loyalty products in the market. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Product Specialist will be involved in meetings with some of the world’s largest retailers and with large potential technology partners, helping to present Perka as part of the full First Data suite of products.  The Product Specialist would need to be intimately familiar with each merchant’s business to tailor his/her content to the specific audience. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The product is a strategic company initiative and this role will have visibility and interaction with senior executives and Executive Committee members. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration:underline&quot;&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Possess intimate knowledge of Perka products and their applicability to different merchant segments &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Build strong knowledge of the loyalty industry including competitor products, offerings, and value propositions &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lead client discussions and communicate compelling Perka selling propositions to merchants &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Work collaboratively with other FDC product teams to present unified pitches to larger clients; understand current and past FDC relationship with each client &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prioritize and synthesize feedback to the product development team to translate into technical specifications &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ensuring there is an understanding and knowledge between merchant requests and the product development team building out functionality &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Build, cultivate, and maintain effective working relationships with relevant stakeholders, including other functional areas within FDC, end-users, project leads, sales and relationship managers and senior executives &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Recommend novel and suitable solutions to complex business, technical, and operational issues presented by clients and prospects &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration:underline&quot;&gt;Requirements&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Candidate should have demonstrated experience leading technology related product initiatives. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;5+ years experience working within a product organization &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;5+ years experience in enterprise sales and relationship management; software/mobile experience preferred &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Strong leadership skills; able to effectively lead efforts across cross functional teams without direct reports &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Strong executive level communication skills and presence (verbal and written) &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Able to prioritize and synthesize client requests and make recommendations for company &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Willingness to roll up sleeves and engage in detailed work &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ability to influence and present compelling sales pitches &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Able to manage multiple projects, priorities, and tasks simultaneously while meeting deadlines &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;** &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;First Data is an Equal Opportunity Employer (Minorities/Females/Vets/Disabled)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </job>
    <job>
      <id>13256276</id>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Big Four practice is composed of more than 2,300 resources with significant industry and technical expertise in a broad range of risk and compliance issues. &lt;br&gt;  &lt;br&gt;They help companies achieve the confidence needed for strong three lines of defense on risk by: &lt;br&gt;  &lt;br&gt;-Building and fortifying internal and IT risk controls &lt;br&gt;  -Developing and strengthening risk and compliance programs &lt;br&gt;  -Improving the capabilities of Internal Audit function &lt;br&gt;  &lt;br&gt;They draw proudly on thier auditing heritage as well as our commercial experience to rigorously evaluate and implement a companies governance procedures, processes, information, and controls. They provide broad support across a business to elevate trust and transparency, protect the business and give all parties assurance that risks are fully anticipated, understood, and managed strategically. &lt;br&gt;  &lt;br&gt;The Risk Assurance practice operates nationally to assist risk, compliance, &amp;amp; finance departments of Fortune 500 companies in using data to make better decisions and get faster results through the use of analytics, strategy, tools and data governance. Within the Financial Services space the team focuses on business topics such as AML, Trade Compliance, Regulatory Reporting and Fraud. Within Healthcare the team is focused on topics such as ICD-10, revenue cycle, meaningful use, PCMH, care coordination, healthcare reform and Fraud. Their services range from hands on analytics to strategy projects related to helping organizations transform themselves to use more analytics across their departments. A sample of their services includes: &lt;br&gt;  &lt;br&gt;- Model Development and Tuning &lt;br&gt;  - System Assessment &lt;br&gt;  - Dashboard Development &lt;br&gt;  - Analytics Strategy &lt;br&gt;  - Continuous Monitoring&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </job>
    <job>
      <id>13256189</id>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;SEAL Consulting Inc is looking to hire Senior / Architect level resources in SAP Hybris area in USA. These resources are expected to work at our client sites in complex system environments.  Candidate should have passion for learning, long term commitment and ability to take up responsibility.  Should be willing to take up new challenges and work on complex issues both independently and as part of a team and should be eager to assume responsibility quickly.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </job>
    <job>
      <id>13256176</id>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;SEAL Consulting Inc is looking to hire Senior and Architect level resources in SAP Ariba in USA. These resources are expected to work at our client sites in complex system environments.  Candidate should have passion for learning, long term commitment and ability to take up responsibility.  Should be willing to take up new challenges and work on complex issues both independently and as part of a team and should be eager to assume responsibility quickly.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </job>
  </jobs>
</job-search>
